

CONTACT

bmc939@gmail.com

github.com/BrandonMCoffey

linkedin.com/in/ brandon-coffey-36a802191

artstation.com/Brandon Coffey

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Dallas

- B. A. in Arts, Technology, and **Emerging Communication – Animation and Games**
- Minor in Computer Science

Allen High School

ABOUT ME

Hello! My name is Brandon and I have a passion for coding and tools development. I have 7+ years of experience with Maya and 2+ years of coding knowledge. Recently I have been devoted to developing games in Unity, as displayed on my portfolio.

BRANDON COFFEY

ANIMATION AND GAMES STUDENT

EXPERIENCE

Portfolio: https://brandonmcoffey.github.io/Portfolio/

Programmer – Telemancer

Fall 2021

Worked as a Unity programmer with a team of 40+ people, building the player systems for the game.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Skilled

- C# (Unity)
- C++
- Java
- SDL Library

Qualified

- Python (Maya)
- HTMI
- Rust

SOFTWARE

Skilled

- Unity (2D, 3D, URP, and HDRP)
- Substance Painter
- Maya (Modeling, Rigging, Shading)
- Adobe Photoshop

Qualified

- Unreal Engine
- Houdini
- After Effects
- Shotgrid

WORK EXPERIENCE

SGDA Officer

Nov. 2021 - Present

Student Game Developer Alliance Club at UTD

La Casita Bakeshop Mar. 2021 - Present

Server - Olive Garden Feb. 2020 - Sep. 2021

Academic Tutor

Oct. 2019 - Dec. 2020

Animation (Modeling, Scripting for Games) Coding (Java, Processing, HTML / CSS) Math (Calculus I, II) and Physics (Mechanics)



















